hi
my name is garland nixon and i'm a
political analyst and i'm john kiriakou
a former cia officer and we've got some
interesting stuff to talk to you about
tonight um very very a tangled web that
we got to talk about i don't think one
show would cover this i don't know if 10
shows would cover it but he'll the uh
the clinton campaign um has been
directly implicated in a plot to um
deliberately paint donald trump as a uh
russian bot so so we'll talk about it
we'll give you a few couple a minute to
go on we'll be right back
[Music]
well john i don't really know where to
start on this so here's what i'm going
to do
i will read the final
a paragraph of the indictment which is
count one in the only count and we'll go
from there
on or about september 19 2016 within the
district of columbia michael a sousman
the defendant did willfully and
knowingly make a materially false
fictitious and fraudulent statement or
representation in a matter before the
jurisdiction of the executive branch of
the government of the united states to
wit
on or about september 19 2016 the
defendant stated to the general counsel
of the fbi that he was not acting on
behalf of any client in conveying
particular allegations concerning a
presidential candidate when in truth and
in fact and as the defendant well knew
knew he was acting on behalf of specific
clients namely tech executive one and
the clinton campaign
like i said this would take a lot of
shows to cover this but let's start john
i'm just gonna throw throw this out on
the floor for the good of the order and
you started what are your thoughts here
you know a couple of things struck me uh
about this indictment first of all it's
27 pages long and a typical indictment
uh for one count of what is known as a
process felony or a throwaway felony
like this one making a false statement
is usually a page long at the most
usually it's a couple of paragraphs you
have sort of the preamble and then the
actual um indicting information
this went on for 27 pages and it's
because they wanted to get all of the
details out there now with that said
the indictment is less important
than the narrative the narrative is
that the clinton campaign corruptly went
to the justice department to accuse the
trump campaign of having either been
infiltrated by the russians or working
in some capacity on behalf of the
russians
uh we know that that's not true we know
now definitively that that's not true
but it it was like the only way to
really get the information out there was
to indict somebody and sussman was the
logical person to indict now
with all that said
this charge is very weak
and the reason why it's weak is that in
this meeting
with
a very senior justice department
official
it was just the two of them right it was
just the doj official
and
uh the attorney sussman
um the doj official did not take notes
what he did was after the meeting he
dictated his recollections from the
meeting to a deputy and the deputy took
the notes
now
the sussman
legal team is going to argue that
these notes were not contemporaneous
that perhaps he misheard what it was
that sussman
wanted to convey
blah blah blah blah
sussman may very well get out of it but
again that's not the point
the point is that
that
special
uh
investigator durham
uh or special prosecutor i i think we're
not supposed to use the term special
prosecutor anymore special investigator
durham
is getting his side of the story out
there so even if this indictment is
thrown out
or if it goes to trial and sussman's
acquitted
it doesn't matter because now we know
exactly how the clinton campaign got to
doj to spread these lies about the
russians
you know the the the thing that stuck in
my mind immediately were were the
connections and that is that at the same
time
and i'll tell you where i'm going with
this
it's hard for me to not to look at this
and think that the fbi is corrupt and
involved in it from top to bottom and
there's so many areas but start here i
don't think it's plausible for the fbi
to argue that they didn't know sussman
was working on behalf of the clinton
campaign simply
because they were working with the with
fusion gps the fbi was working with
fusion gps who was and fusion gps was
working for the clinton campaign and let
me add one more thing
the fbi
the doj i don't know if it was exactly
the fbi or somebody up in the doj but at
any rate wrote up it was the fbi they
wrote up a fisa uh one
they took it to the fisa court and in
that warrant they did the exact same
thing that they're accusing michael
sussman of
they hid from the fisa court and we know
because that's in the ig horowitz
report
they the the fbi hid
from the fisa judges
that christopher steele's uh information
was paid for by the clinton campaign
so they did exactly yes what they're
saying they're going after sussman for
and both grew in susman was working with
fusion gps i just feel like it was one
big criminal operation and one part of
the big opportunity to let susan go they
gotta let him walk this guy they can't
nobody can go down because one person
could bring everybody down
no you're exactly right i'm so glad that
you said what you said because i was
gonna i was gonna raise this same thing
the fbi and the just and the justice
department knew
that the steele dossier had begun as
opposition research and that the source
of the steele dossier was the clinton
campaign now you remember in the very
beginning that the clinton campaign um
put out this rumor that it actually
originated with with a republican
campaign and they hinted that it was ted
cruz that was nonsense
there was a relationship between
christopher steele and the clinton
people and that resulted in the steele
dossier the clinton people knew that the
dossier was made up right they knew that
it was just unvetted raw intelligence
the purpose of which was to make donald
trump look as bad as they possibly could
and they presented it to the justice
department as fact as finished
intelligence and it wasn't it never was
yeah and the other thing is um
look i mean there's just so many facets
of this but when you look at at
there's tech executive one i don't know
who it is but you know no idea as an old
investigator here as an old investigator
let me tell you where i'd start snooping
around
so this investigator this person
apparently has the ability to do cyber
investigations don't they
they were searching dnf look at the
things that they were doing right
whoever this person is this person can
do cyber investigations
so we know whoever tech executive is one
is they're probably pretty good with
cyber investigations all right
we do also know if we research carefully
we find out that michael sussman
was the guy
who hired
crowdstrike
for the dnc correct right
owned by dimitri alparovich and sean
what's his name
a former fbi agent right
and oh wait a minute what's crowdstrike
do cyber investigation
as an old investigation i have no idea
who it is
but i would go to crowdstrike and start
questioning people there yeah perhaps
they'd know someone who could do cyber
investigations who was closely connected
to the clinton campaign and who maybe
perhaps was connected directly to
michael sussman that's where i'd start
snooping around as an old investigator
but what do i know i'm retiring i i
think you've cracked the case and you
know one of our one of our viewers
melinda ann burns makes a very good
point that i'd like to repeat here she
says these people are always going after
the low-hanging fruit no bigwigs ever
get charged convicted or punished and
she is exactly right do you have any
idea what the sentencing guideline is
for this crime now this is a felony
let's make a wild assumption that
michael sussman is going to be convicted
the sentencing guideline for a first
time conviction on this
low-hanging felony
is zero to six months in prison with six
months being if you have a prior
criminal record
so even if they
if they convict this guy which they
won't
he's not going anywhere near a prison is
this really worth the taxpayers money
this investigation has been going on for
four and a half years
now if if your intent is to expose the
clinton campaign then by god
congratulations you've you've
accomplished your mission and the
country is better for it but don't make
it look like this is you know you're
tracking down
the big wig criminals you're not
well you know
what i think is going on here and you
know i guess i'm going down conspiracy
theory lane but if you look at the
evidence i'm not
what i think where where they're jammed
up is this
i mean the fbi was part of the operation
clearly let me add this okay
so we have
fusion gps and perkins coi so fusion gps
produces the steele dossier perkins
chord produces this
alpha bank scandal both of them
scandal but if you read the steele
dossier there's one little section in
there
that says alpha bank and then it says
putin's buddy
is an alpha bank and that guy handles
like a hundred thousand dollars cash and
hands it out to people for putin he's
putin's bag man putin's money man right
but there's nothing else in there about
that and you look at that and you're
saying well what the hell is that doing
in the steele dossier is there something
connected to it
it's nothing it's just
and you're like what the hell and now
you look at this and you're like okay
it doesn't align with anything else in
the steele dossier that aligns perfectly
with the argument that they were making
it perkins coy so they were just running
parallel tracks here and they were the
same and when you look at the emails and
the meetings they were the same people
working together they probably wrote
those documents in the same room
together and passed them around each
other
they probably did and it just goes to
show you
the the depths to which the the dnc
and the 2016 clinton campaign uh would
plunge
and this is something we ought to we
ought to be talking about i mean not
just you and me but as a nation we
should talk about the dnc as a as a
political machine and the rnc for that
matter because god knows that the
republicans do exactly the same kind of
thing this is the problem that we've
gotten ourselves into in this country
with with a duopoly
that we have where the two parties just
trade positions back and forth every
couple of years this doesn't serve the
american people in any way it encourages
corruption
yep
let me let me share here's something
this is this is off of the document and
this is something that i want to ask you
about let's give me a second here i got
to share the screen all righty
all right john
so if we look down here what we find is
that um
okay section 35 order about october 30th
on a unemployed an employee of the u.s
investigative firm
appears to be fusion gps forwarded
another report a reporter a tweet which
indicated that the fbi director had
explosive information about trump's ties
to russia the investigative firm's
employee email stated time to hurry
suggesting the reporters should hurry to
publish an article regarding the russian
bank allegations in response reporter 2
emailed to the investigative firm
employee a draft article regarding the
russia bank allegations along with the
cover message here's the first 2500
words
the
the um
let me
stop sharing here so
the clinton campaign was literally just
planting stories in the media the media
is sending them articles here's the
first 2500 words does this work it's
that's the other part of the corruption
it's not just that they were trying to
get hillary clinton elected okay that we
know that
but they were willing to participate in
corruption corruption that could end up
dragging us into a nuclear war nuclear
war we're talking about corruption where
you're creating enmity with
a a nuclear power that is every bit as
powerful as you are with nuclear weapons
either one of them could take us out the
the recklessness of that is is just uh
unfathomable and this points to another
very serious problem and that is
collusion between uh between members of
the media
and uh and the federal government
we know thanks to to the intrepid jason
leopold at buzzfeed uh the king of the
freedom of information act request we
know we know
thanks to him that msnbc's ken delanian
or nbc news is ken delanian their chief
national security correspondent
um was sending his articles to the cia
before he was sending them to his own
editor
this is what they do you know rather
than than to develop your own sources
a la
woodward and bernstein back in the day
uh they just rely on whatever the ucia
the fbi and the white house tell them
you know it's like taking a a press
release and just gisting it and putting
it into your own words and then calling
it news it's not news well this is yet
another example of that
and they have the nerve to show i mean
clint watts sure you know who that is
clint watts literally went before
congress and argued that a facebook
group
that had pictures of puppies was russian
election interference because what they
were planning on doing see well you
don't understand how devious the
russians are john that's your problem
you're too naive and gullible they were
going to take these pictures of puppies
and then once people got hooked on the
puppies they were going to little by
little start putting um
uh uh
political messages etc i guess maybe the
puppies would all get together and spell
borscht or something who knows right i
mean and make you love russia exactly
subliminally the preposterous things
they put together
and argue that's election interference
dude this is election interference at
the highest level they literally to me
the here's what i think the
federal election commission should go
after them because clearly that was done
as part of their election campaign and
how do we know that because it was paid
for out of the funds of the election
coffers so the fact of the matter is
this
what are you doing you
in the course of your think about that
that money came directly out of the
election coffers what can you buy if you
were to purchase drugs heroin with money
that people had donated to you you could
go to jail for that if you were to use
that money to violate the law
i would argue the fec should be
investigating did they use um campaign
money to do something that was criminal
and well we got what at least part of it
was criminal but i'm sure they could dig
and find other parts of it that i could
i bet you that your thoughts
oh i think you're exactly right
and this goes back to uh to that comment
that we read a few minutes ago they go
after the low-hanging fruit not not the
big players
um there's
literally no reason
why the fec should not be going after
the clinton campaign and going after the
clinton campaign's you know campaign
chairman
the campaign manager maybe hillary
clinton herself if if she had something
to do with the with the planning of this
thing
why isn't there an fec
investigation why isn't there a
congressional investigation why aren't
the oversight committees involved that's
a huge point i didn't even think about
that right now
congress should be saying we're
concerned with election interference we
can't exactly write so we got to look
because that was clearly they utilized
use the media i mean the problem is this
i think when i look at this this thing
was written up like how can we just make
sure we have a name attached to this
we're not going to be able to do this
without a name
and
there was too much dirt for whatever
reason durham wanted to get this story
out i don't know how much i trust him or
anybody else but i'm glad a lot of this
information got out
this is the same john durham who refused
to charge any of the torturers involved
in the cia's torture campaign right this
is the guy that refused to charge the
likes of john brennan and jose rodriguez
and these and these monsters at the cia
who dragged our national reputation
through the mud 10 years ago
right but but this crime he'll charge
that doesn't make any sense to me i look
at him like bar
barr has a long history he's an
operative i think durham is an operative
and i think this is for whatever reason
they didn't mind getting this out maybe
they just felt like look we're gonna
have to take some blood and we're gonna
have to lose some blood we'll lose
minimum amount of blood we'll go ahead
look this is making the 2016 hillary
campaign look bad right hillary ain't
running no more and it ain't 2016. so as
long as they don't charge any of these
people but in a blink of an eye it was
seven eight years ago right so that all
walks this guy he's playing
don't forget they filed these charges
just two days before the statute of
limitations expired yep
two days
i mean here's the thing he gets next to
nothing anyway and to me it's part of an
operation here's see they can't go after
anybody they have to have somebody agree
to say i'll be the one because they were
working with the fbi and everybody knew
it it was part of an fbi operation think
about this when you when it goes to this
how close can we get to sussman and uh
assessment in the fbi
so susman was working with perkins coy
and fusion gps if you look at it they
were like meeting they were emailing
back and forth they were working
together on an operation fusion gps they
were being paid by the same clients this
was an operation that they were being
paid together to work together okay
so those two are working together
meanwhile the cia claims to us that they
dropped christopher steele but one of
the doj lawyers a guy named bruce orr
his wife was working for fusion gps so
you mean to tell me the doj had one of
their people's wives working for for for
using gps
and fusion gps was working directly with
sussman every day and she didn't know
the sussman was working for the clinton
campaign she was working with him and
the clinton campaign her husband's a doj
lawyer he didn't somehow figure it out
either the fbi the evidence they were
they were drowning in evidence but they
didn't see it john
you know if it wasn't so serious it
would be hilarious
and when you lay it all out like you
just did in plain english it sounds so
ridiculous
that
it can't be true right
but all of it is true all of it's true
where we're supposed to believe that the
right hand doesn't know what the left
hand is doing
that
when husbands and wives you know go home
at the end of the work day
they don't have any idea what each other
was doing during the course of the day
they don't even know where their spouses
work
right
one of the fbi is looking at the clinton
campaign the other one's working for a
contractor for the clinton campaign uh
they're the the campaign people are
talking to the fbi the fbi people are
talking to the campaign and they just
pretend that everything is all fine and
good and normal and legal
which is what the real problem is
and we only find out about this now
years after the fact that's unacceptable
and during the same investigation let's
not forget so during this investigation
look at some of the things that happened
susman supposedly hid that he was
working for the clinton camp campaign
right
the fbi hid that steele was working for
the clinton campaign
so the fbi and cis-men are all working
together they also tried to hide
that they were still working with steele
that was a hot they were hiding that
that's why it went from
okay you talked to an fyei agent into to
okay you talked to the wife
of a doj lawyer who passes it on to her
who now so all they did was put a middle
person in in in between steel yes there
that's all they did it was obvious and
deliberate deliberate what they were
doing and look who's been fired mccabe
was fired for lying
um but not prosecuted right uh uh comey
was run out the door for lion
i mean not prosecuted so
right those two guys were run out from
line but not prosecuted regarding the uh
the the trump russian investigation
kevin kleinsmith was prosecuted for
deliberately lying and might i had
mccabe and
uh comey should have both been um
uh prosecuted for deliberately lying
they were perjury they deliberately
signed off on documents knowingly and
lied to the fisa court on several
occasions every one of those is a
separate charge and that's and each one
of those is a felony that carries with
it up to five years in a federal prison
so why weren't they charged why weren't
they prosecuted you know too big to
prosecute come on
we're not supposed to have people like
that in the united states yep so so if
you look at the the the trump russia
investigation
a lot of the people that were heavily
involved peter strzok run out the door
for lying and cheating stealing
everything you name it right
a lot a lot of the people that have
involved have been caught in wrongdoing
directly related to that here's what i
hope happens
but i don't trust our courts enough
anyway i hope trump sees every one of
them
i don't i think you know some of those
in particular groups are
are well i don't know because a lot of
times like the uh um government agencies
or personnel will be immune from immune
from um from being sued right yeah but
then at the same time at the same time
if you sue the campaign you sue the
clinton campaign right then you're
entitled to discovery and then that all
of this comes out into the public well
that's what i was thinking he couldn't
necessarily probably see the people but
he could write zeus men he could sue the
people at gps he could do all of them
and in discovery you know so everybody
that he can touch that he sues and i
hope he does because discovery now
really
what you'll find
they can't do it you know if this will
be a rare instance where they'll do a
pull of hillary clinton i mean let's
face it she just saw it destroyed 33 000
emails and her only option was to go to
jail if she didn't and sometimes people
have an option you ask for discovery and
it's like well let's see if i give you
the murder weapon right i'm going to
jail i'll throw that in the river yeah i
never saw it that's right
that's right that's washington that's
how things work here it's been like this
uh you know since the beginning really
the important people get away with it
they get away with everything
yeah you know let me ask you this uh uh
uh um
because you know as i said i don't have
any idea who tech executive one
is i have no idea who he is who he was
but
let's just say that
if it's
as i said susan has has connections to
um to
direct connections to uh a crowd strike
so we don't know if
i have no i'm not going to imply in any
way i think it's them but i'm just
saying that
another
thing that i think would be a point of
evidence i don't know what it says but i
think this would be a point of evidence
and that is
the um
uh uh uh um
if i if
if they knew who he was if he was in any
way connected to uh to to to that to to
um if the and of course they know who he
was but if the
if by any way shape or form the
tech executive one had some connection
to them
right
then i would have to again say to the
fbi
shouldn't you revisit your decision
not to look at the dnc servers
if they were involved with people
cooking up this stuff yeah
and you expect me to believe and
again it points to the fbi they were
working for susman
they think about this they work for
susman
the fbi
trusted them the fbi didn't require any
forensic evidence from them didn't even
they were told that they were going to
get a draft report we learned that
during the roger stone trial they didn't
get a draft report basically the fbi had
word of mouth
from crowd strike and they took word of
mouth to argue that the you know the
whole dnc server thing by word of mouth
if there was any connection i'll put it
like this i i again
another point of evidence that makes me
suspect there could be a connection or
to say a a reasonable lawyer should at
least
pursue that that in the investigation
yeah you know this is something that we
we really have to remember and that is
after the dnc hack after the dnc
realized that it had been hacked
and the fbi was brought in the dnc still
refused to give the fbi access to the
servers
the fbi said that they couldn't do an
investigation without access to the
server so the dnc said that they would
provide copies of the servers for the
fbi to investigate that never happened
and the and the dnc has never
explained to anybody even to their own
constituents that is democrats
why they refused to cooperate with the
fbi what was it that they had to hide
we've never learned that
and they what did you know this did you
know they went to servers
that doesn't surprise you they wiped the
servers yeah so they never they never
i'm handing them over but that's fine
look they i i understand that them
saying they want okay that's that that
that's fine but you know you you work
for an intelligence agent i work for law
enforcement
if i walk on that scene and i'm whoever
i'm fbi
and they're like yeah we think they were
penetrated by you know whoever you know
the russians the chinese whoever anybody
right
i'm putting a couple of uh agents on
their servers nobody comes near it till
i go get a warrant and when i come back
we're taking those servers exactly right
for permission now i put two
uh agents they're guarding the door one
of their somebody's standing right
beside the servers nobody comes near
there i am leaving this is a crime scene
put the tape up when i get back we're
going to take those servers i'm not
asking you for them this is a national
security issue and i'm calling national
i'm calling nsa i'm calling the other
intern the national security experts and
say we need your best people the nsa the
best people you got we need to look at
the server immediately and i'm not
asking and i'm not hey garland did you
get the server well i asked him but they
wouldn't give it to you get out of here
with that silliness john
and that never happened garland
the fbi never never put its foot down
the fbi never sought a warrant the fbi
just as you said they shrug their
shoulders and said well we asked them
for the server they wouldn't give it to
us so we're going to go over here on to
this
other case we're just going to forget
about this one that's really what
happened here
i mean you and i would call that a
cover-up
the media just says well you know
everybody did what they thought was in
their best interests
yep if some guy right now it's supposed
to work
if some if some guy right now in in
northwest dc had child porn on his
laptop and they found out about it
they'd break the door down grab him
laptop if he had a hard network hard
drive every computer in the house and
off they'd go they would knock on the
door excuse me sir can we come in so
if you would do that for a
just the possession of child porn you're
not going to tell me that you wouldn't
do that for potential um uh uh uh uh
espionage for you know any whatever for
some kind of a potential uh uh uh
infiltration from a foreign entity yes
yeah you're exactly right you know if
this is the national security threat
that everybody wants to believe it is
the the fbi should have been like this
on white on like white on rice and as
you said a moment ago it bears repeating
the fbi should have called every top
national security analyst and
investigator with specialization
in in cyber security and in forensic
investigations to get to the bottom of
this and believe me i've worked with
these guys i know how smart they are how
capable they are they could have cracked
this what years ago
years ago there's no reason for us four
and a half years later to be sitting
here speculating this should all be
public information by now
yeah i i i will be very interested when
we find out and
and
the and and the other thing is tech
executive one we also find out in the
charging document
that he expected to get a cushy job
in the clinton
again i think to myself hmm
so whoever this is whatever the clinton
p people or the dnc wanted
he's gonna
point in that direction and if you think
about it if you're playing this game
well i'm going to say russia these guys
these guys this thing's going to go out
this is going to say trump and alpha
bank now in the steel document we're
going to put out that
there's a bad guy for putin with alpha
bank now over here we're going to say
the russians um they hacked into the
server and blah blah blah but it the
problem the issue is it's not plausible
for anybody who's ever worked in
intelligence or in law enforcement to
believe that the fbi would accept it in
an obviously a criminal or
internationally criminal espionage case
whatever you know that they would accept
a private company
that they would accept their word of
what they found on the server and never
get it first of all that they'd accept
their word okay
but for this reason
how do you know how if you're the fbi if
it's me and i go there and i'm like hey
who'd you get we got crowd strike hey we
think we're hit by the russians or
whoever right i'm here's the first thing
i have to think i don't know the crowd
strike is not inside people on the bad
guys i don't know that crowdstrike
didn't come in and they're the ones that
opened the door and let them in i don't
have to i'm not can't trust crowdstrike
hey i guess you're the good guy hell no
that's not the way it works when you're
doing investigation so i'm not gonna
bring
the fox in to investigate the in-house
murders i'm gonna say crowdstrike oh
they got hit
i'm not eliminating them as a suspect
i'm not eliminating anybody as a suspect
as i said when i start looking at that
servers i want to talk to crowdstrike
and interview them and say i want to
know what you did to these servers
you've you've already examined them
before we got here i want to know what
you did i want to see what you did i
want to see everything the results of
everything
or your ass has gone to jail because
this is a national security issue right
now so don't hold your breath so the
idea
that the
fbi would just trust a private company
to use their
and add this
because the data that you're using here
could be eventually be used to prosecute
somebody
but it couldn't because you don't have
any data because all you've got is a a a
witness so if like some russian guy from
dc knocked on their off door and said
guys it's me i'm uh you know a spy from
whatever country i did it i'm guilty
yeah they couldn't prosecute them with
that evidence because they have none
they have none and i've got to ask too
and this is not a rhetorical question
but why in the world would a senior doj
official
meet with somebody with anybody let
alone with a senior partner from perkins
coy
and not have a note taker
not have a witness or even not have it
recorded
right i mean that's what the fbi does
that's what they're supposed to do all
the time
but here's the number three or number
four in the justice department and he's
just winging it has a guy over to his
office they chew the fat for a little
bit the guy essentially
confesses to a crime in the course of
the conversation and they're not going
to take notes they're going to dictate
the notes a little bit later just to the
best of their recollection and then
charge a felony out of it this is like
amateur hour over there at the justice
department
it is but when it it it is if you
believe their narrative right you know
what i mean right
perhaps there there is something for
them to gain by making themselves look
stupid in this case well what's the
alternative you know what i mean yeah
the alternative is you can't charge
anybody right and the alternative is
that you find out who was involved in
this with the clinton people and i i
mean when i look at comey i look at his
history i look at his fealty to hillary
i just got to say this guy was working
with the clinton campaign i just
believed that the entire time
um i don't trust him i don't trust any
of them and
um mccabe all of them and here's the
here's another tell that that the
machine was hiding for itself
robert mueller or it wasn't really
mueller it was the other guy really that
did an investigation they just stamped
mueller's name on it yeah but
was it 20 or 40 000 text messages
between peter strzok and his girlfriend
and the investigation's going on mueller
finds them and i've never heard of this
before so in the midst of the evidence
of the investigation mueller has a
critical piece of evidence which is the
text messages between
two um fbi employees who are at the
heart of the investigation
so man that's critical evidence
and he erases it all and he erases it
erases it yeah
destruction of evidence is a felony yes
yeah and have you read anyone but one in
the media hey why'd you do that yeah no
nobody cares
nobody cares no
in any other in the other country this
would be an explosive front page
story
it would shake
confidence in government in any other
country and here people are like eh you
know business as usual that's a swamp
in a way
what you're saying is true and
indicative of
a
collapsing i'm going to just be straight
out a collapsing empire and what i mean
is this
the people of the empire
have lost faith in the institutions that
hold the empire together that make this
culture right people have lost faith
so when they hear corruption it's like
hey boy that was short corrupt and
people are like and you expected
something else out of washington d.c
really right i'm going i got to go play
pickleball they're gone they'd rather go
play pickleball what do they care
because they know that what do you go
what's going to happen tomorrow well
we're going to leave one of the
countries that we invaded and we're
going to find out that we laundered um
two and a half trillion dollars into the
hands of the
the war profiteers that'll happen next
week and then the week after some other
corruption will come out yes
yes welcome to washington
yeah well thanks a lot john we're at
well a long room this is 40 minutes but
uh you know we had plenty we had a lot
to talk about we didn't touch nearly on
some of the other stuff but we'll keep
all this i'm sure some other things will
pop up i'm rendering just wondering you
and i are wondering
who could tech executive one be
hmm
somebody is gonna leak it it's
washington
yeah they are and man that's a that is a
huge one got to tell you that all right
thanks a lot thanks a lot everybody coop
dub thanks everybody
michael melinda and burns she's always
out there peace john and i are out